<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>list on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</title>
    <link>https://joshuacasey.net/tags/list/</link>
    <description>Recent content in list on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joshuacasey.net/tags/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts I listen to and recommend</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/podcasts-i-listen-to-and-recommend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/podcasts-i-listen-to-and-recommend/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to podcasts for a couple years. Most of the time when listening to a podcast I will be driving a virtual truck making virtual deliveries either in Euro Truck Simulator 2 or, more recently, in American Truck Simulator. Over the course of roughly about the past year I started listening to my podcasts at 1.5x speed so that it takes less time to listen to the episodes. It sounds a little funny at first, but you get use to it surprisingly quick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I can&#39;t live without</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</guid>
      <description>1. Dogs As I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before numerous times on the Internet I am autistic. My life definitely made an improvement after we got our first dog. When she&amp;rsquo;s in the same room as me I feel more comfortable. And if someone else is in the room talking to me, I can focus my attention and look at or pet the dogs, which makes me feel pretty much 110% more comfortable. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I want to ever try to live without a dog in my life ever again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of the Apps 2018</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/state-of-the-apps-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/state-of-the-apps-2018/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the end of the year. I would like to take some time to review some of the apps that I have installed on my phone that I consider worth recommending. I will maybe separate this into separate categories: productivity, messaging, social, financial, and possibly &amp;ldquo;honorary mentions&amp;rdquo;.
Productivity   Todoist
This is probably my favorite to-do list app. And they recently added a dark mode which I greatly appreciate as a necessary accessibility feature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
