<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</title>
    <link>https://joshuacasey.net/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joshuacasey.net/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Job</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/my-dream-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/my-dream-job/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent way too much time trying to think about what my dream job would be. When you&amp;rsquo;re autistic like I am it&amp;rsquo;s a daily struggle to live in a world that is not built for people like you and a world that is constantly fighting against you. Personally, I know that because of some of the difficulties that I have from being autistic, I could never have a &amp;ldquo;traditional&amp;rdquo; job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I can&#39;t live without</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</guid>
      <description>1. Dogs As I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before numerous times on the Internet I am autistic. My life definitely made an improvement after we got our first dog. When she&amp;rsquo;s in the same room as me I feel more comfortable. And if someone else is in the room talking to me, I can focus my attention and look at or pet the dogs, which makes me feel pretty much 110% more comfortable. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I want to ever try to live without a dog in my life ever again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did I start blogging</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/why-did-i-start-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/why-did-i-start-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Over the years of my life I have tried many times to start blogging and do it on a frequent basis. All previous attempts have never really been a success. There are a couple of reasons why I decided to start writing blog posts on this website. The first reason is that I host this website myself (for free). I don&amp;rsquo;t have to rely on Wordpress or Tumblr or any other blogging platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is making friends so hard</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/why-is-making-friends-so-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/why-is-making-friends-so-hard/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure why I&amp;rsquo;m writing something so personal. Mostly I have a lot of anxious thoughts that I need to get out of my head and nobody to talk to. This seems like the only place where I can turn. December has been one hell of an anxious month. It all started a couple days after the month began, when this really kind person that I met on Twitter blocked me on Twitter and Instagram for an unknown reason.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
