<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</title>
    <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Joshua Casey - Autistic Activist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joshuacasey.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Dream Job</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/my-dream-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/my-dream-job/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent way too much time trying to think about what my dream job would be. When you&amp;rsquo;re autistic like I am it&amp;rsquo;s a daily struggle to live in a world that is not built for people like you and a world that is constantly fighting against you. Personally, I know that because of some of the difficulties that I have from being autistic, I could never have a &amp;ldquo;traditional&amp;rdquo; job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts I listen to and recommend</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/podcasts-i-listen-to-and-recommend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/podcasts-i-listen-to-and-recommend/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to podcasts for a couple years. Most of the time when listening to a podcast I will be driving a virtual truck making virtual deliveries either in Euro Truck Simulator 2 or, more recently, in American Truck Simulator. Over the course of roughly about the past year I started listening to my podcasts at 1.5x speed so that it takes less time to listen to the episodes. It sounds a little funny at first, but you get use to it surprisingly quick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things I can&#39;t live without</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/things-i-cant-live-without/</guid>
      <description>1. Dogs As I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned before numerous times on the Internet I am autistic. My life definitely made an improvement after we got our first dog. When she&amp;rsquo;s in the same room as me I feel more comfortable. And if someone else is in the room talking to me, I can focus my attention and look at or pet the dogs, which makes me feel pretty much 110% more comfortable. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I want to ever try to live without a dog in my life ever again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did I start blogging</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/why-did-i-start-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/august/why-did-i-start-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Over the years of my life I have tried many times to start blogging and do it on a frequent basis. All previous attempts have never really been a success. There are a couple of reasons why I decided to start writing blog posts on this website. The first reason is that I host this website myself (for free). I don&amp;rsquo;t have to rely on Wordpress or Tumblr or any other blogging platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to protect yourself online</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/april/how-to-protect-yourself-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2019/april/how-to-protect-yourself-online/</guid>
      <description>So much of our lives involves the Internet. Whether we are using our computers at work or at home. Or using our phones. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine how we would function without the Internet at our fingertips. Whether we&amp;rsquo;re catching up with the latest social media trends, catching up on email, checking our calendars, or any of the other numerous tasks that we may use our devices for, protecting our digital privacy and security may be one of the most important things we can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of the Apps 2018</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/state-of-the-apps-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/state-of-the-apps-2018/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the end of the year. I would like to take some time to review some of the apps that I have installed on my phone that I consider worth recommending. I will maybe separate this into separate categories: productivity, messaging, social, financial, and possibly &amp;ldquo;honorary mentions&amp;rdquo;.
Productivity   Todoist
This is probably my favorite to-do list app. And they recently added a dark mode which I greatly appreciate as a necessary accessibility feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Bucket List</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/my-bucket-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/my-bucket-list/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of lists, checklists, and to-do lists. It&amp;rsquo;s only natural that the idea of a &amp;ldquo;bucket list&amp;rdquo; is something that I am a fan of. Here is mine (I will probably update it frequently so feel free to check back from time to time):
 First IRL/non-Internet friend. First kiss. First relationship. Own a Tesla. Visit all 48 of the Continental United States. (maybe on a road trip?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I do when setting up a new linux server</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/what-i-do-when-setting-up-a-new-linux-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/what-i-do-when-setting-up-a-new-linux-server/</guid>
      <description>This post is a bit more techy. If that&amp;rsquo;s not something that interests you, sorry&amp;hellip;but this is my blog so I get to decide what content is on here. I thought I would write a post detailing the process that I go through when I set up a new linux server (either a remote server or re-installing my Raspberry Pi&amp;hellip;which I will actually be doing very soon, probably in less than 6 hours).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is making friends so hard</title>
      <link>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/why-is-making-friends-so-hard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joshuacasey.net/posts/2018/december/why-is-making-friends-so-hard/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure why I&amp;rsquo;m writing something so personal. Mostly I have a lot of anxious thoughts that I need to get out of my head and nobody to talk to. This seems like the only place where I can turn. December has been one hell of an anxious month. It all started a couple days after the month began, when this really kind person that I met on Twitter blocked me on Twitter and Instagram for an unknown reason.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
